pokemondeluge.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy - DelugeRPG

The user agrees that the use of DelugeRPG's services (Game site, forums and wiki) is entirely at the user's own risk. DelugeRPG's services are provided on an 'as is' basis without warranties of any kind. DelugeRPG makes no guarantee of availability of service and reserves the right to change or remove any functionality or feature of DelugeRPG's services. In no event shall DelugeRPG be liable for any damages arising out of the use of or inability to use DelugeRPG's services or any content there on. The user is responsible for any activity that occurs under their account and that they are responsible for keeping their accounts and passwords secure.

When you visit our website, DelugeRPG does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, or phone number. 

Access to your account is by way of username and password (or single sign-ons such as yahoo,facebook and google) and it is your responsibility to keep these safe and secure. We will not restore any accounts if you fail to do so.   
Never share your password with absolutely anyone, even if they claim to be admins or staff. Real admins do not need a password to access your account.

Your emails are only used for password recovery,in case you forget your password. They will never be sold, or given to any third-party. Also, emails will never be displayed in your profile when others view it.   
Accounts without any email associated with their account cannot be recovered.

We may delete your account if it has been more than 15 months from your last login (Please log in atleast once a year to keep your account). However, if an account has not been used since the day of registration, it may be deleted within 3 months.

To catch scammers and phishers, our systems may scan messages to warn the receiver of the message. We are not responsible if your account gets stolen. [Learn how you can keep your account safe](https://www.delugerpg.info/Protecting_your_Account).

On a side node, Banned accounts will not be restored. And Deleted accounts cannot be restored.

DelugeRPG, like many other sites, uses 'cookies' to store session data to allow you to stay logged in. This is pretty much all we do with cookies here. If the media has scared you into thinking cookies are evil or use of cookies is not acceptable by you, and is disabled on your browser, you will not be able to register or login.

Google Analytics uses a number of cookies to determine unique users, keep track of pages within a given site and how you arrived at our Website. You can opt out of Google Analytics cookies by visiting <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.   
To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

We have included links on this site for your use and reference (pokemon related sites , social networking sites). We are not responsible for the content and privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of DelugeRPG then you may contact us at - **admin@delugerpg.com**

We are not affiliated with [Nintendo](http://www.nintendo.com/ "Nintendo"), [The Pokémon Company](http://www.pokemon.com/ "Pokemon") [Creatures Inc.](http://www.creatures.co.jp/ "Creatures Inc.") or [Game Freak](http://www.gamefreak.co.jp/ "Game Freak"). No copyright or trademark infringement is intended.

Pokémon, all Pokémon names, all Pokémon images, and related names used are copyright: Gamefreak, Nintendo of America, Nintendo of Japan, Creatures and it's respective owners.

Note that DelugeRPG is only a fan-site, kept running only with whatever is made from the advertisements on the site. We do not ask or accept any sort of donations.

We do not sell any in-game pokemon or items. So, Please do not email us offering "donations" (in exchange for in-game stuff or otherwise).

We urge you to purchase the actual pokemon video games. They should be easily available at your country's [Amazon](https://www.amazon.com/) (Recommended), [Ebay](https://www.ebay.com/) or similar online stores, if they are not available at any local stores.

[Last updated August 2014]
